<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<tables>
    <table>
        <list>
            <item><weight>15</weight><name>+1 Weapon</name><type>Weapon</type><desc>You have a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>8</weight><name>+1 Tool/Kit</name><type>Tool/Kit</type><desc>You have a +1 bonus to rolls made with this magic tool or kit.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>8</weight><name>Wand of the War Mage, +1</name><type>Wand</type><desc>While you are holding this wand, you gain a +1 bonus to spell attack rolls. In addition, you ignore half cover when making a spell attack.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Pearl of Power</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While this pearl is on your person, you can use an action to speak its command word and regain one expended spell slot. If the expended slot was of 4th level or higher, the new slot is 3rd level. Once you have used the pearl, it can't be used again until the next dawn.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Instrument, +1</name><type>Instrument</type><desc>You have a +1 bonus to performance, song of rest, and bardic inspiration rolls made with this magic instrument.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Mariner’s Armor</name><type>Armor</type><desc>While wearing this armor, you have a swimming speed equal to your walking speed. In addition, whenever you start your turn underwater with 0 hit points, the armor causes you to rise 60 feet toward the surface. The armor is decorated with fish and shell motifs.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Boots of Striding and Springing</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While you wear these boots, your walking speed becomes 30 feet, unless your walking speed is higher, and your speed isn't reduced if you are encumbered or wearing heavy armor. In addition, you can jump three times the normal distance, though you can't jump farther than your remaining movement would allow.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Boots of the Winterlands</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>These furred boots are snug and feel quite warm. While you wear them, you gain the following benefits: You have resistance to cold damage. You ignore difficult terrain created by ice or snow. You can tolerate temperatures as low as -50 degrees Fahrenheit without any additional protection. If you wear heavy clothes, you can tolerate temperatures as low as -100 degrees Fahrenheit.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Gloves of Swimming and Climbing</name><type></type><desc>While wearing these gloves, climbing and swimming don't cost you extra movement, and you gain a +5 bonus to Strength (Athletics) checks made to climb or swim.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Boots of Elvenkind</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While you wear these boots, your steps make no sound, regardless of the surface you are moving across. You also have advantage on Dexterity (Stealth) checks that rely on moving silently.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Gloves of Thievery</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>These gloves are invisible while worn. While wearing them, you gain a +5 bonus to Dexterity (Sleight of Hand) checks and Dexterity checks made to pick locks.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Rope of Climbing</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>This 60-foot length of silk rope weighs 3 pounds and can hold up to 3,000 pounds. If you hold one end of the rope and use an action to speak the command word, the rope animates. As a bonus action, you can command the other end to move toward a destination you choose. That end moves 10 feet on your turn when you first command it and 10 feet on each of your turns until reaching its destination, up to its maximum length away, or until you tell it to stop. You can also tell the rope to fasten itself securely to an object or to unfasten itself, to knot or unknot itself, or to coil itself for carrying. If you tell the rope to knot, large knots appear at 1-foot intervals along the rope. While knotted, the rope shortens to a 50-foot length and grants advantage on checks made to climb it. The rope has AC 20 and 20 hit points. It regains 1 hit point every 5 minutes as long as it has at least 1 hit point. If the rope drops to 0 hit points, it is destroyed.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Wand of Magic Missiles</name><type>Wand</type><desc>This wand has 7 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 or more of its charges to cast the magic missile spell from it. For 1 charge, you cast the 1st-level version of the spell. You can increase the spell slot level by one for each additional charge you expend. The wand regains 1d6 + 1 expended charges daily at dawn. If you expend the wand's last charge, roll a d20. On a 1, the wand crumbles into ashes and is destroyed.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Wind Fan</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While holding this fan, you can use an action to cast the gust of wind spell (save DC 13) from it. Once used, the fan shouldn't be used again until the next dawn. Each time it is used again before then, it has a cumulative 20 percent chance of not working and tearing into useless, nonmagical tatters.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Brooch of Shielding</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While wearing this brooch, you have resistance to force damage, and you have immunity to damage from the magic missile spell.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Bracers of Archery</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While wearing these bracers, you have proficiency with the longbow and shortbow, and you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls on ranged attacks made with such weapons.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Hat of Disguise</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While wearing this hat, you can use an action to cast the disguise self spell from it at will. The spell ends if the hat is removed.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Sentinel Shield</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While holding this shield, you have advantage on initiative rolls and Wisdom (Perception) checks. The shield is emblazoned with a symbol of an eye.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Amulet of Proof Against Detection and Location</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While wearing this amulet, you are hidden from divination magic. You can't be targeted by such magic or perceived through magical scrying sensors.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Cloak of Elvenkind</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While you wear this cloak with its hood up, Wisdom (Perception) checks made to see you have disadvantage, and you have advantage on Dexterity (Stealth) checks made to hide, as the cloak's color shifts to camouflage you. Pulling the hood up or down requires an action.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Gauntlets of Ogre Power</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>Your Strength score is 19 while you wear these gauntlets. They have no effect on you if your Strength is already 19 or higher without them.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Slippers of Spider Climbing</name><type>Wonderous Item</type><desc>While you wear these light shoes, you can move up, down, and across vertical surfaces and upside down along ceilings, while leaving your hands free. You have a climbing speed equal to your walking speed. However, the slippers don't allow you to move this way on a slippery surface, such as one covered by ice or oil.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Staff of the Adder</name><type>Staff</type><desc>You can use a bonus action to speak this staff's command word and make the head of the staff become that of an animate poisonous snake for 1 minute. By using another bonus action to speak the command word again, you return the staff to its normal inanimate form. You can make a melee attack using the snake head, which has a reach of 5 feet. Your proficiency bonus applies to the attack roll. On a hit, the target takes 1d6 piercing damage and must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or take 3d6 poison damage. The snake head can be attacked while it is animate. It has an Armor Class of 15 and 20 hit points. If the head drops to 0 hit points, the staff is destroyed. As long as it's not destroyed, the staff regains all lost hit points when it reverts to its inanimate form.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Staff of the Python</name><type>Staff</type><desc>You can use an action to speak this staff's command word and throw the staff on the ground within 10 feet of you. The staff becomes a giant constrictor snake under your control and acts on its own initiative count. By using a bonus action to speak the command word again, you return the staff to its normal form in a space formerly occupied by the snake. On your turn, you can mentally command the snake if it is within 60 feet of you and you aren't incapacitated. You decide what action the snake takes and where it moves during its next turn, or you can issue it a general command, such as to attack your enemies or guard a location. If the snake is reduced to 0 hit points, it dies and reverts to its staff form. The staff then shatters and is destroyed. If the snake reverts to staff form before losing all its hit points, it regains all of them.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Wand of Web</name><type>Wand</type><desc>This wand has 7 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 of its charges to cast the web spell (save DC 15) from it. The wand regains 1d6 + 1 expended charges daily at dawn. If you expend the wand's last charge, roll a d20. On a 1, the wand crumbles into ashes and is destroyed.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Weapon of Warning</name><type>Weapon</type><desc>This magic weapon warns you of danger. While the weapon is on your person, you have advantage on initiative rolls. In addition, you and any of your companions within 30 feet of you can't be surprised, except when incapacitated by something other than nonmagical sleep. The weapon magically awakens you and your companions within range if any of you are sleeping naturally when combat begins.</desc></item>
        </list>
        <list>
            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Weapon, +2</name><type></type><desc>You have a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Giant Slayer</name><type></type><desc>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.  When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Lightning Spike Weapon, +1</name><type></type><desc>This +1 weapon shimmers with yellow light when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as lightning damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Flame Tongue Weapon, +1</name><type></type><desc>This +1 weapon bursts into flame when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as fire damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Freezing Brand Weapon, +1</name><type></type><desc>This +1 weapon glows to reveal a rune when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as ice damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Culling Weapon, +1</name><type></type><desc>This +1 weapon sublimates fumes when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as acid damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Tacticians Weapon, +1</name><type></type><desc>This +1 weapon flashes with light when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can activate your chosen battlemaster manuever.  Each tactician weapons bestows knowledge of a particlar manuever, and grants an additional superiority dice, which is a d6 if you do not already have one</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Cloaked Weapon, +1</name><type></type><desc>This +1 weapon is invisible to everyone but the creature attuned it. As the wielder of the weapon, you gain advantage with melee attacks made using the weapon until you successfully hit, at which point the weapon becomes visible to everyone.  A cloaked weapon turns invisible again after being sheathed for a short rest (5 minutes).</desc></item>

            <item><weight>20</weight><name>Armor, Shield, +1</name><type></type><desc>You have a +1 bonus to AC while wearing this armor.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Ratform Armor</name><type></type><desc>Once per day, you can use an action to use the Polymorph spell. This polymorph spell can only transform you to a common sewer rat. While in this form: -You can't attack. -Your gear is unusable. -You gain a +5 bonus to Dexterity(Stealth) checks  You can sustain this power as an action on your turn and end the power to return to your normal form as a free action.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Armor/Shield of [Damage Type] Resistance</name><type></type><desc>You have resistance to [Damage Type] damage while you wear this armor.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Bracers of Defense</name><type></type><desc>While wearing these bracers, you gain a +2 bonus to AC if you are wearing no armor and using no shield.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>15</weight><name>Tool/Kit, +2</name><type></type><desc>You have a +2 bonus to rolls made with this magic tool or kit.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Quarterstaff of Ancients, +1</name><type></type><desc>While holding this staff, you gain a +1 bonus to spell attack rolls and to the saving throw DCs of your warlock spells.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>15</weight><name>Wand of the War Mage, +2</name><type></type><desc>While you are holding this wand, you gain a +2 bonus to spell attack rolls. In addition, you ignore half cover when making a spell attack.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Instrument, +2</name><type></type><desc>You have a +2 bonus to performance, song of rest, and bardic inspiration rolls made with this magic instrument.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Ring of [Damage Type] Resistance</name><type></type><desc>You have resistance to [Damage Type] damage while wearing this ring.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Ring of Free Action</name><type></type><desc>While you wear this ring, difficult terrain doesn't cost you extra movement. In addition, magic can neither reduce your speed nor cause you to be paralyzed or restrained.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Ring of Feather Falling</name><type></type><desc>When you fall while wearing this ring, you descend 60 feet per round and take no damage from falling.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Ring of Evasion</name><type></type><desc>This ring has 3 charges, and it regains 1d3 expended charges daily at dawn. When you fail a Dexterity saving throw while wearing it, you can use your reaction to expend 1 of its charges to succeed on that saving throw instead.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Broom of Flying</name><type></type><desc>his wooden broom, which weighs 3 pounds, functions like a mundane broom until you stand astride it and speak its command word. It then hovers beneath you and can be ridden in the air. It has a flying speed of 50 feet. It can carry up to 400 pounds, but its flying speed becomes 30 feet while carrying over 200 pounds. The broom stops hovering when you land.  You can send the broom to travel alone to a destination within 1 mile of you if you speak the command word, name the location, and are familiar with that place. The broom comes back to you when you speak another command word, provided that the broom is still within 1 mile of you.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Amulet of Health</name><type></type><desc>Your Constitution score is 19 while you wear this amulet. It has no effect on you if your Constitution score is already 19 or higher without it.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Arrow-catching Shield</name><type></type><desc>You gain a +2 bonus to AC against ranged attacks while you wield this shield. This bonus is in addition to the shield's normal bonus to AC. In addition, whenever an attacker makes a ranged attack against a target within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to become the target of the attack instead.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Belt of Dwarvenkind</name><type></type><desc>While wearing this belt, you gain the following benefits:  Your Constitution score increases by 2, to a maximum of 20.  You have advantage on Charisma (Persuasion) checks made to interact with dwarves.  In addition, while attuned to the belt, you have a 50 percent chance each day at dawn of growing a full beard if you're capable of growing one, or a visibly thicker beard if you already have one.  If you aren't a dwarf, you gain the following additional benefits while wearing the belt:  You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage.  You have darkvision out to a range of 60 feet.  You can speak, read, and write Dwarvish.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Berserker Axe</name><type></type><desc>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, while you are attuned to this weapon, your hit point maximum increases by 1 for each level you have attained.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Boots of Levitation</name><type></type><desc>While you wear these boots, you can use an action to cast the levitate spell on yourself at will.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Gem of Seeing</name><type></type><desc>This gem has 3 charges. As an action, you can speak the gem's command word and expend 1 charge. For the next 10 minutes, you have truesight out to 120 feet when you peer through the gem.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Horn of Blasting</name><type></type><desc>You can use an action to speak the horn's command word and then blow the horn, which emits a thunderous blast in a 30-foot cone that is audible 600 feet away. Each creature in the cone must make a DC 15 Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 5d6 thunder damage and is deafened for 1 minute. On a successful save, a creature takes half as much damage and isn't deafened. Creatures and objects made of glass or crystal have disadvantage on the saving throw and take 10d6 thunder damage instead of 5d6.  Each use of the horn's magic has a 20 percent chance of causing the horn to explode. The explosion deals 10d6 fire damage to the blower and destroys the horn.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Cloak of Protection +1</name><type></type><desc>You gain a +1 bonus to AC and saving throws while you wear this cloak.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Boots of Speed</name><type></type><desc>While you wear these boots, you can use a bonus action and click the boots' heels together. If you do, the boots double your walking speed, and any creature that makes an opportunity attack against you has disadvantage on the attack roll. If you click your heels together again, you end the effect.  When the boots' property has been used for a total of 10 minutes, the magic ceases to function until you finish a long rest.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Ring of the Ram</name><type></type><desc>This ring has 3 charges, and it regains 1d3 expended charges daily at dawn. While wearing the ring, you can use an action to expend 1 to 3 of its charges to attack one creature you can see within 60 feet of you. The ring produces a spectral ram's head and makes its attack roll with a +7 bonus. On a hit, for each charge you spend, the target takes 2d10 force damage and is pushed 5 feet away from you.  Alternatively, you can expend 1 to 3 of the ring's charges as an action to try to break an object you can see within 60 feet of you that isn't being worn or carried. The ring makes a Strength check with a +5 bonus for each charge you spend.</desc></item>
        </list>
        <list>
            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Weapon, +3</name><type></type><desc>You have a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Giant Slayer +2</name><type></type><desc>You gain a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.  When you hit a giant with it, the giant takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, "giant" refers to any creature with the giant type, including ettins and trolls.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Lightning Spike Weapon, +2</name><type></type><desc>This +2 weapon shimmers with yellow light when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as lightning damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Flame Tongue Weapon, +2</name><type></type><desc>This +2 weapon bursts into flame when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as fire damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Freezing Brand Weapon, +2</name><type></type><desc>This +2 weapon glows to reveal a rune when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as cold damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Culling Weapon, +2</name><type></type><desc>This +2 weapon sublimates fumes when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the total damage as acid damage</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Tacticians Weapon, +2</name><type></type><desc>This +2 weapon flashes with light when its command word is spoken.  When activated in this way, you can activate your chosen battlemaster manuever.  Each tactician weapons bestows knowledge of a particlar manuever, and grants an additional superiority dice, which is a d6 if you do not already have one</desc></item>
            <item><weight>4</weight><name>Cloaked Weapon, +2</name><type></type><desc>This +2 weapon is invisible to everyone but the creature attuned it. As the wielder of the weapon, you gain advantage with melee attacks made using the weapon until you successfully hit, at which point the weapon becomes visible to everyone.  A cloaked weapon turns invisible again after being sheathed for a short rest (5 minutes).</desc></item>

            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Crystal Ball</name><type></type><desc>This crystal ball is about 6 inches in diameter. While touching it, you can cast the scrying spell (save DC 17) with it.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Ring of Regeneration</name><type></type><desc>While wearing this ring, you regain 1d6 hit points every 10 minutes, provided that you have at least 1 hit point. If you lose a body part, the ring causes the missing part to regrow and return to full functionality after 1d6 + 1 days if you have at least 1 hit point the whole time.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Ring of Shooting Stars</name><type></type><desc>While wearing this ring in dim light or darkness, you can cast dancing lights and light from the ring at will. Casting either spell from the ring requires an action.  The ring has 6 charges for the following other properties. The ring regains 1d6 expended charges daily at dawn. Faerie Fire (1)  Ball Lightning (2) Shooting Stars (1-3)</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Ring of Telekinesis</name><type></type><desc>While wearing this ring, you can cast the telekinesis spell at will, but you can target only objects that aren't being worn or carried.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Robe of Scintillating Colors</name><type></type><desc>This robe has 3 charges, and it regains 1d3 expended charges daily at dawn. While you wear it, you can use an action and expend 1 charge to cause the garment to display a shifting pattern of dazzling hues until the end of your next turn. During this time, the robe sheds bright light in a 30-foot radius and dim light for an additional 30 feet. Creatures that can see you have disadvantage on attack rolls against you. In addition, any creature in the bright light that can see you when the robe's power is activated must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or become stunned until the effect ends.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>2</weight><name>Robe of Stars</name><type></type><desc>This black or dark blue robe is embroidered with small white or silver stars. You gain a +1 bonus to saving throws while you wear it.  Six stars, located on the robe's upper front portion, are particularly large. While wearing this robe, you can use an action to pull off one of the stars and use it to cast magic missile as a 5th-level spell. Daily at dusk, 1d6 removed stars reappear on the robe.  While you wear the robe, you can use an action to enter the Astral Plane along with everything you are wearing and carrying. You remain there until you use an action to return to the plane you were on. You reappear in the last space you occupied, or if that space is occupied, the nearest unoccupied space.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Rod of absorption</name><type></type><desc>While holding this rod, you can use your reaction to absorb a spell that is targeting only you and not with an area of effect. The absorbed spell's effect is canceled, and the spell's energy—not the spell itself—is stored in the rod. The energy has the same level as the spell when it was cast. The rod can absorb and store up to 50 levels of energy over the course of its existence. Once the rod absorbs 50 levels of energy, it can't absorb more. If you are targeted by a spell that the rod can't store, the rod has no effect on that spell.  When you become attuned to the rod, you know how many levels of energy the rod has absorbed over the course of its existence, and how many levels of spell energy it currently has stored. If you are a spellcaster holding the rod, you can convert energy stored in it into spell slots to cast spells you have prepared or know. You can create spell slots only of a level equal to or lower than your own spell slots, up to a maximum of 5th level. You use the stored levels in place of your slots, but otherwise cast the spell as normal. For example, you can use 3 levels stored in the rod as a 3rd-level spell slot. A newly found rod has 1d10 levels of spell energy stored in it already. A rod that can no longer absorb spell energy and has no energy remaining becomes nonmagical.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Rod of Alertness</name><type></type><desc>This rod has a flanged head and the following properties.  Alertness.  While holding the rod, you have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks and on rolls for initiative.  Spells.  While holding the rod, you can use an action to cast one of the following spells from it: detect evil and good, detect magic, detect poison and disease, or see invisibility  Protective Aura.  As an action, you can plant the haft end of the rod in the ground, whereupon the rod's head sheds bright light in a 60-foot radius and dim light for an additional 60 feet. While in that bright light, you and any creature that is friendly to you gain a +1 bonus to AC and saving throws and can sense the location of any invisible hostile creature that is also in the bright light.  The rod's head stops glowing and the effect ends after 10 minutes, or when a creature uses an action to pull the rod from the ground. This property can't be used again until the next dawn.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Rod of Security</name><type></type><desc>While holding this rod, you can use an action to activate it. The rod then instantly transports you and up to 199 other willing creatures you can see to a paradise that exists in an extraplanar space. You choose the form that the paradise takes. It could be a tranquil garden, lovely glade, cheery tavern, immense palace, tropical island, fantastic carnival, or whatever else you can imagine. Regardless of its nature, the paradise contains enough water and food to sustain its visitors. Everything else that can be interacted with inside the extraplanar space can exist only there. For example, a flower picked from a garden in the paradise disappears if it is taken outside the extraplanar space. For each hour spent in the paradise, a visitor regains hit points as if it had spent 1 Hit Die. Also, creatures don't age while in the paradise, although time passes normally. Visitors can remain in the paradise for up to 200 days divided by the number of creatures present (round down).  When the time runs out or you use an action to end it, all visitors reappear in the location they occupied when you activated the rod, or an unoccupied space nearest that location. The rod can't be used again until ten days have passed.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Staff of Fire</name><type></type><desc>You have resistance to fire damage while you hold this staff. The staff has 10 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 or more of its charges to cast one of the following spells from it, using your spell save DC: burning hands (1 charge), fireball (3 charges), or wall of fire (4 charges). The staff regains 1d6 + 4 expended charges daily at dawn. If you expend the last charge, roll a d20. On a 1, the staff blackens, crumbles into cinders, and is destroyed.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Staff of Frost</name><type></type><desc>You have resistance to cold damage while you hold this staff. The staff has 10 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 or more of its charges to cast one of the following spells from it, using your spell save DC: cone of cold (5 charges), fog cloud (1 charge), ice storm (4 charges), or wall of ice (4 charges). The staff regains 1d6 + 4 expended charges daily at dawn. If you expend the last charge, roll a d20. On a 1. the staff turns to water and is destroyed.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Staff of Power</name><type></type><desc>This staff can be wielded as a magic quarterstaff that grants a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it. While holding it, you gain a +2 bonus to Armor Class, saving throws, and spell attack rolls.  The staff has 20 charges for the following properties. The staff regains 2d8 + 4 expended charges daily at dawn. If you expend the last charge, roll a d20. On a 1, the staff retains its +2 bonus to attack and damage roll but loses all other properties. On a 20, the staff regain 1d8 + 2 charges.  Power Strike.  When you hit with a melee attack using the staff, you can expend 1 charge to deal an extra 1d6 force damage to the target.  See Item Desc in book for more.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>3</weight><name>Staff of Striking</name><type></type><desc>This staff can be wielded as a magic quarterstaff that grants a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it.  The staff has 10 charges. When you hit with a melee attack using it, you can expend up to 3 of its charges. For each charge you expend, the target takes an extra 1d6 force damage. The staff regains 1d6 + 4 expended charges daily at dawn. If you expend the last charge, roll a d20. On a 1, the staff becomes a nonmagical quarterstaff.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Staff of Thunder and Lightning</name><type></type><desc>This staff can be wielded as a magic quarterstaff that grants a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it. It also has the following additional properties. When one of these properties is used, it can't be used again until the next dawn.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>15</weight><name>Armor, Shield, +2</name><type></type><desc>You have a +2 bonus to AC while wearing this armor.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Armor/Shield of [Damage Type] Resistance +1</name><type></type><desc>You have resistance to [Damage Type] damage while you wear this +1 armor.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>1</weight><name>Cloak of Protection +2</name><type></type><desc>You gain a +2 bonus to AC and saving throws while you wear this cloak.</desc></item>

            <item><weight>15</weight><name>Tool/Kit, +3</name><type></type><desc>You have a +3 bonus to rolls made with this magic tool or kit.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>10</weight><name>Quarterstaff of Ancients, +2</name><type></type><desc>While holding this staff, you gain a +2 bonus to spell attack rolls and to the saving throw DCs of your warlock spells.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>15</weight><name>Wand of the War Mage, +3</name><type></type><desc>While you are holding this wand, you gain a +3 bonus to spell attack rolls. In addition, you ignore half cover when making a spell attack.</desc></item>
            <item><weight>5</weight><name>Instrument, +3</name><type></type><desc>You have a +3 bonus to performance, song of rest, and bardic inspiration rolls made with this magic instrument.</desc></item>
        </list>
    </table>
</tables>